[
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 0:18:55",
   "QKEY":"Q1",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Killrrhubarb",
   "GameTitle":"The Dream Machine",
   "Question":"What two materials make up The Dream Machine's aesthetic?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Cardboard & Clay",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wool & Fabric",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Metal & Rock",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ice & Snow",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 0:36:39",
   "QKEY":"Q2",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Asterioncrest",
   "GameTitle":"Star Ocean 3: Til The End Of Time",
   "Question":"In Star Ocean 3, what is the alarming fact that the party learns about their Universe?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"That it is a video game",
   "FakeAnswer1":"That it is collapsing",
   "FakeAnswer2":"That it is being conquered by darkness",
   "FakeAnswer3":"That the planets were dying",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 0:47:42",
   "QKEY":"Q3",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"thetoughestbean ",
   "GameTitle":"Omikron: The Nomad Soul",
   "Question":"What artist released an original song for David Cage's first game, Omikron?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"David Bowie",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Michael Jackson",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Prince",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Paul McCartney",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 0:51:22",
   "QKEY":"Q4",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Iron Chitlin",
   "GameTitle":"Diablo 2",
   "Question":"Who is the last of the Horadrim?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Deckard Cain",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Halbu",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Asheara",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Qual-Kehk",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 0:54:16",
   "QKEY":"Q5",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"thetoughestbean ",
   "GameTitle":"Sonic Rush",
   "Question":"Which character is an alternate dimension version of Sonic the Hedghog in this DS title?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Blaze the Cat",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Silver the Hedgehog",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shadow the Hedgehog",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sonic from an actually good game series",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 0:58:40",
   "QKEY":"Q6",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Sid Meier's Civilization V",
   "Question":"Which expansion introduced the espionage mechanic?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Gods & Kings",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Brave New World",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Beyond the Sword",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Rising Tide",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 1:03:38",
   "QKEY":"Q7",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MetaMarx",
   "GameTitle":"Cave Story",
   "Question":"What's the first step in getting the best ending?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Skip the Booster 0.8",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Retrieve the tow cable",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Restore Curly Brace's memory",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Defeat the Doctor",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 3:56:21",
   "QKEY":"Q8",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"ColonelPanic",
   "GameTitle":"Donkey Kong Country",
   "Question":"What does the 'K' stand for in the name King K. Rool?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Krusha",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Kremling",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Klomp",
   "FakeAnswer3":"K. Rool",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 20:57:17",
   "QKEY":"Q9",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Tyndolionel",
   "GameTitle":"Power Instict (SNES)",
   "Question":"What is the given name of the playable Granny?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Otane (oh-tah-nay)",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Kyouko (keeyoh-koh)",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Oume (owe-may)",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Margaret",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 21:21:07",
   "QKEY":"Q10",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Super Metroid",
   "Question":"Which area can you find the Gravity Suit?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Wrecked Ship",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Crateria",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Maridia",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Norfair",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 21:50:19",
   "QKEY":"Q11",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man 8",
   "Question":"Whose stage has Yoku Blocks (disappearing blocks)?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Astro Man",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Clown Man",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Grenade Man",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sword Man",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/7/2015 22:56:14",
   "QKEY":"Q12",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Super Mario Bros. 2",
   "Question":"When changing Doki Doki Panic to SMB2 for America, which character was the base for Luigi?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Mama",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Papa",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lina",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Imajin",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/8/2015 0:05:53",
   "QKEY":"Q13",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Castlevania: Symphony of the Night",
   "Question":"Which Belmont do you control in the prologue and also has a mode where you play as him for the whole game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Richter",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Julius",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Trevor",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Simon",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/8/2015 23:33:08",
   "QKEY":"Q14",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Zelda: A Link to the Past",
   "Question":"Which of the three medallions is not required to beat the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bombos",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Quake",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ether",
   "FakeAnswer3":"You need all of them",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/9/2015 2:09:15",
   "QKEY":"Q15",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Paper Mario: The 1000 Year Door",
   "Question":"What is your prize for reaching the 30th floor of the Pit of 100 Trials?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Zap Tap",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Pity Flower",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Fire Drive",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Double Dip",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/14/2015 20:32:39",
   "QKEY":"Q16",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Gerk",
   "GameTitle":"Mario Kart 8",
   "Question":"Which of the following Marios is not a playable character?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Fire Mario",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Cat Mario",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tanooki Mario",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Metal Mario",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/18/2015 20:07:17",
   "QKEY":"Q17",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Lolo De Puzlo",
   "GameTitle":"Blaster Master",
   "Question":"What was the protagonist chasing that started his whole adventure?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"His pet frog Fred",
   "FakeAnswer1":"His girlfriend Eve",
   "FakeAnswer2":"His son Roddy",
   "FakeAnswer3":"His pet rabbit Daisy",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/24/2015 10:47:26",
   "QKEY":"Q18",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Smite",
   "GameTitle":"Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars",
   "Question":"Who was the chef that, along with his apprentice, accidentally created a wedding cake monster?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Chef Torte",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Chef Crepe",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Chef Bundt",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Chef Galette",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"11/24/2015 19:01:35",
   "QKEY":"Q19",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Bebuva",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy IX",
   "Question":"What card game do you unlock after entering a code after the ending credits in FFIX?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"BlackJack",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Rummy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Poker",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Solitaire",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/5/2015 22:54:53",
   "QKEY":"Q20",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Babycowland",
   "GameTitle":"Club Drive",
   "Question":"What's the full name of the level \"____ Pad\"?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Jerome's",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Bill's",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Jack's",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sam's",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/5/2015 23:42:20",
   "QKEY":"Q21",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Babycowland",
   "GameTitle":"Super Smash Bros. for 3DS/Wii U",
   "Question":"Which of the following characters was in Brawl, but is not playable in Smash for 3DS/Wii U?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Ice Climbers",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Young Link",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lucario",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Dr. Mario",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/6/2015 6:45:32",
   "QKEY":"Q22",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Vectorman ",
   "Question":"Which of the following is not a transformation power-up in Vectorman?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A Glove",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A Bomb",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Rocket ",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A Drill",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/6/2015 11:58:17",
   "QKEY":"Q23",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Super Mario World",
   "Question":"What order do you find the Switch Palaces in?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Yellow, Green, Red, Blue",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Yellow, Red, Blue, Green",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Yellow, Red, Green, Blue",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Yellow, Blue, Green, Red",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/6/2015 15:34:40",
   "QKEY":"Q24",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Monster Rancher 2",
   "Question":"What rare item increases a monster's lifespan by 50 weeks?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Golden Peach",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Phoenix Feather",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Heart Pill",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sparkling Elixir",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/7/2015 15:08:14",
   "QKEY":"Q25",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"GuyVett",
   "GameTitle":"World of Illusion",
   "Question":"What is the item that gives Mickey and Donald an extra try?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tophat",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Slice of cake",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mickey's and Donald's decapitated heads",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Magic wand",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/10/2015 20:28:03",
   "QKEY":"Q26",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Revenge of Shinobi",
   "Question":"Which of these classic pop culture icons was not a boss in Revenge of Shinobi?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Freddy Krueger",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Spiderman",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Terminator",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Godzilla",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/10/2015 20:51:34",
   "QKEY":"Q27",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Gnoll Queen",
   "GameTitle":"Dark Souls",
   "Question":"What is the only class in Dark Souls that starts at soul level 1?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pyromancer",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Deprived",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Thief",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bandit",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/10/2015 21:18:58",
   "QKEY":"Q28",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Gnoll Queen",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy: Four Heroes of Light ",
   "Question":"In Final Fantasy: Four Heroes of Light Beelzebub appears as a:",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A Crowned infant-faced Tentacle monster",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A Fly/Wasp monster with a Crown",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Four armed sexy lady with a proboscis sticking out of her mouth (And a crown on her head)",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A Penguin with a Crown",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/11/2015 13:13:48",
   "QKEY":"Q29",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Phoenix Wright: Trials and Tribulations",
   "Question":"Who uses the pseudonum \"Elise Deauxnim\" when they visit Hazakura Temple in Case 5?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Misty Fey",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Maya Fey",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dahlia Hawthorne",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pearl Fey",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/12/2015 21:46:23",
   "QKEY":"Q30",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"D_W",
   "GameTitle":"Uniracers",
   "Question":"What company sued Rockstar North (then DMA Design) over the display of animated unicycles?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pixar",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Warner Bros.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Disney",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Nickelodeon",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/13/2015 20:20:12",
   "QKEY":"Q31",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man 2 (NES)",
   "Question":"What is the only weapon that can harm the final boss (the alien hologram)?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bubble Lead",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Quick Boomerang",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Metal Blade",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Air Shooter",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/13/2015 21:43:09",
   "QKEY":"Q32",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Binding of Isaac: Rebirth",
   "Question":"Which item can repel projectiles?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Soul",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Halo",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Relic",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Wafer",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/14/2015 19:43:50",
   "QKEY":"Q33",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Lolo De Puzlo",
   "GameTitle":"Castlevania",
   "Question":"Which of these games is not a direct retelling of the story told in the first Castlevania game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Castlevania: Lords of Shadow",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Super Castlevania IV",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Haunted Castle",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Castlevania Chronicles",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/20/2015 19:35:37",
   "QKEY":"Q34",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"applecat78",
   "GameTitle":"PokÃ©mon X and Y",
   "Question":"What type is Zygarde? ",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Dragon / Ground",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Poison / Dragon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ghost / Dark",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Dragon",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 3:02:27",
   "QKEY":"Q35",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Legend of Grimrock",
   "Question":"Which of the following tools is not used in the game for a mobile light device?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Lantern",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Orb",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Magic",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Orb",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 4:36:18",
   "QKEY":"Q36",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Baloney Amputation",
   "GameTitle":"Lufia 2 (SNES)",
   "Question":"Which dirty-sounding item is actually present in the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Lizard Blow",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Slick Rod",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Meat Goo",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bull Poker",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 14:35:08",
   "QKEY":"Q37",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Pikmin (series)",
   "Question":"What is the name of the iconic pikmin monster that is just a mouth with eyestalks and tiny legs?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Spotty Bulborb",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Snitchbug",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Dumple",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Burrowing Snagret",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 15:07:10",
   "QKEY":"Q38",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"Duke Nukem 3D",
   "Question":"Which of these is the boss of Episode 1 - LA Meltdown? ",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Battlelord",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Overlord",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Cycloid Emperor",
   "FakeAnswer3":"An evil Duke Nukem",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 15:30:42",
   "QKEY":"Q39",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"The Binding of Isaac Rebirth",
   "Question":"You've just collected a Goat Head. What does it do?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Guarantees angel/devil rooms",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Protects you from Mom's stomps",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Reduces the prices of devil deals",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tricks Satan into believing you're his son",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 17:33:36",
   "QKEY":"Q40",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"ProtoIV",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy V",
   "Question":"Which job is NOT gained from the Wind Crystal?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Red Mage",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Blue Mage",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Monk",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Thief",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 23:37:31",
   "QKEY":"Q41",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"Lemmings",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a skill you can assign to Lemmings?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Runner",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Builder",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bomber",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Blocker",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/22/2015 23:44:40",
   "QKEY":"Q42",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Gourmet Sentai - Bara Yarou",
   "Question":"What is the name of the female player character?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Madame",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lady",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Parfait",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ma'am",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 0:10:33",
   "QKEY":"Q43",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Devious Vacuum",
   "GameTitle":"Octodad",
   "Question":"What is Octodad's wife's name?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Scarlet",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Charlotte",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Debra",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ursula",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 0:22:53",
   "QKEY":"Q44",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Devious Vacuum",
   "GameTitle":"Bomberman 64: The Second Attack!",
   "Question":"What is the name of Bomberman's companion in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pommy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Temmie",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Boomer",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Gubby",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 0:36:35",
   "QKEY":"Q45",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Devious Vacuum",
   "GameTitle":"Heavy Rain",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a kid who died in Heavy Rain?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Jayden",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Jason",
   "FakeAnswer2":"John",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jeremy",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 5:17:17",
   "QKEY":"Q46",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Midwoka",
   "GameTitle":"Star Fox",
   "Question":"Which member of Star Wolf used to work alongside Peppy and Fox's dad?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pigma",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Andrew",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Leon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Panther",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 5:28:37",
   "QKEY":"Q47",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Midwoka",
   "GameTitle":"Yoshi's Island",
   "Question":"When you touch Fuzzy, you...",
   "CorrectAnswer":"...get dizzy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"...rock the party",
   "FakeAnswer2":"...feelin' sad",
   "FakeAnswer3":"...find religion",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 19:32:11",
   "QKEY":"Q48",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"Pilotwings",
   "Question":"Who's your instructor for Lesson 4?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Big Al",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lance",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tony",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Shirley",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 20:42:28",
   "QKEY":"Q49",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Witcher 3",
   "Question":"Which enemy is a boss?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Plague Maiden",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Noonwraith",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Alghoul",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Hound of the Wild Hunt",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 21:00:20",
   "QKEY":"Q50",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"IronCastKnight",
   "GameTitle":"Sports Classics",
   "Question":"On the NES, which of these games combined together an internationally popular sport, intense hand to hand combat, and a deep team management mode?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Base Wars",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Super Dodge Ball",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mega Man Soccer",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ring King",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/23/2015 22:30:24",
   "QKEY":"Q51",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"donkeyboat",
   "GameTitle":"Castlevania: Aria of Sorrow",
   "Question":"Which recurring enemy is first encountered as a boss?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Big Golem",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Werewolf",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Final Guard",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Man-Eater",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/24/2015 20:35:47",
   "QKEY":"Q52",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Telltale's Game of Thrones",
   "Question":"Which character from the show does not make an appearance in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sansa Stark",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Jon Snow",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tyrion Lannister",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Danaerys Targaryen",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/24/2015 22:02:37",
   "QKEY":"Q53",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mjolna",
   "GameTitle":"X-COM: Terror From the Deep",
   "Question":"Which is not an enemy in game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Thin Man",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lobster Man",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Gill Man",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Xarquid",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/24/2015 22:53:34",
   "QKEY":"Q54",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mjolna",
   "GameTitle":"Ratchet & Clank",
   "Question":"What does RYNO stand for?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Rip Ya a New One",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Nothing",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rockets You kNow Of",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Rhino ",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/25/2015 2:15:22",
   "QKEY":"Q55",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Kapitan Tripp",
   "GameTitle":"Age of Empires 2",
   "Question":"Which of the following Civilizations was added in \"The Conquerors\" expansion?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Koreans",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Vikings",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Incans",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Ethiopians",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 0:13:05",
   "QKEY":"Q56",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Godzillan",
   "GameTitle":"Dota 2",
   "Question":"As Invoker, how do you invoke Ice Wall?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Quas Quas Exort",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Quas Quas Wex",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Quas Wex Exort",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Exort Exort Wex",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 3:08:25",
   "QKEY":"Q57",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mjolna",
   "GameTitle":"Neko Atsume",
   "Question":"Which of these cats wields a sword?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"SeÃ±or Don Gato",
   "FakeAnswer1":"SeÃ±or Don Cato",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Muskateer Cathos",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Catsbalger",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 11:43:55",
   "QKEY":"Q58",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Heroes of the Storm",
   "Question":"The hero Cho'Gall has a gimmick never before seen in any MOBA. What is his gimmick?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Two players play him simultaneously",
   "FakeAnswer1":"His strength stays the same as the game goes on",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The player cannot control his movement directly",
   "FakeAnswer3":"He is technically a member of the opposing team",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 17:12:22",
   "QKEY":"Q59",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Gnoll Queen",
   "GameTitle":"Sword of Vermilion",
   "Question":"What is the 3rd most powerful type of Kobold?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Hyena Kobold",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wolf Kobold",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Coyote Kobold",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tiger Kobold ",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 19:26:15",
   "QKEY":"Q60",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Warhammer: Dawn of War",
   "Question":"Which of these factions was added to the game in the Dark Crusade expansion pack?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Necrons",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Imperial Guard",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tyranids",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sisters of Battle",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 21:23:52",
   "QKEY":"Q61",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Mutant League Football",
   "Question":"Which of these teams was not based on a real NFL team?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"War Slammers",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Icebay Bashers",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Slaycity Slayers",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Misfit Demons",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 21:49:53",
   "QKEY":"Q62",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Super Street Fighter 2: The New Challengers",
   "Question":"Who was the only character to be designed by Capcom Of America?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Dee Jay",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Cammy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"T. Hawk",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Fei Long",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 22:19:30",
   "QKEY":"Q63",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Dota 2",
   "Question":"Which neutral creep doesn't have an active ability?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Alpha Wolf",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mud Golem",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Centaur Conqueror",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Hellbear Smasher",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/26/2015 23:19:14",
   "QKEY":"Q64",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"THErealDRAGON",
   "GameTitle":"Psychonauts",
   "Question":"In the Milkman Conspiracy what is needed to pass \"Road Crew Workers?\"",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A Red Sign",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A High Visablity Vest",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Shovel",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A phone",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/28/2015 13:33:42",
   "QKEY":"Q65",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Downwell",
   "Question":"What is the name of the 2nd location in the Downwell well?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Catacomb",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dungeon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Chamber",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Factory",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/28/2015 23:20:10",
   "QKEY":"Q66",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Super Mario RPG",
   "Question":"Name the weird marionette enemy seen in Smithy's factory.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Puppox",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Remo Con",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Marion",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Neo Con",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/30/2015 15:19:26",
   "QKEY":"Q67",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Greenflame1971",
   "GameTitle":"Dragon quest VI",
   "Question":"Who is the only character to learn Magic Burst without use of the Liquid Metal Slime vocation?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Ashlynn",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Milly",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Nevan",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Kingsley",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/30/2015 20:18:44",
   "QKEY":"Q68",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"WesSchneider",
   "GameTitle":"Astyanax",
   "Question":"The name \"Astyanax\" comes from a character in _______ Mythology.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Greek",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Slavic",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Catalan",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Persian",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"12/30/2015 20:35:09",
   "QKEY":"Q69",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"WesSchneider",
   "GameTitle":"Clash at Demonhead",
   "Question":"In Clash at Demonhead, what's the name of the professor you're trying to save?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Professor Plum",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Professor Umbridge",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Professor Emeritus",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Professor Zoom",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/1/2016 5:03:19",
   "QKEY":"Q70",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Civilization II",
   "Question":"Which of the following is NOT a wonder in Civ II?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Stonehenge",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Globe Theater",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Cure for Cancer",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Newton's College",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/1/2016 5:17:28",
   "QKEY":"Q71",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"NeoTM",
   "GameTitle":"Earthbound",
   "Question":"What is the name of the Bee in the opening sequence of Earthbound?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Buzz-Buzz",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Buzzy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Buzzter",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Buzzor",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/1/2016 13:26:16",
   "QKEY":"Q72",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Lolo De Puzlo",
   "GameTitle":"Mana series",
   "Question":"The first game in the Mana series was referred to as what when it came to the US?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Final Fantasy Adventure",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Final Fantasy: Mystic Quest",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Final Fantasy Legend",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Seiken Psycho Calibur",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/2/2016 18:40:42",
   "QKEY":"Q73",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo-Tooie",
   "Question":"The HAG-1 drilling machine crashed through what color Jinjo house in Banjo Tooie?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Grey",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Red",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Orange",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Brown",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/3/2016 14:00:19",
   "QKEY":"Q74",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"Deus Ex",
   "Question":"What is Anna Navarre's killphrase?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Flatlander Woman",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Nuts and Bolts",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Laputan Machine",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bionic Highlander",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/4/2016 20:10:55",
   "QKEY":"Q75",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Shiva Asori",
   "GameTitle":"Eternal Ring",
   "Question":"During the course of the plot, you meet several dragons. Which one do you fight as a boss battle?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Wind Dragon",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Fire Dragon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Water Dragon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Earth Dragon",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/9/2016 23:16:46",
   "QKEY":"Q76",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"AndyAML",
   "GameTitle":"Cybernator",
   "Question":"Where does the second stage of the game take place?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"An asteroid field",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A space colony",
   "FakeAnswer2":"An Earth military base",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A black hole",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/10/2016 23:07:03",
   "QKEY":"Q77",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Smash Daisaku",
   "GameTitle":"Gunstar Heroes",
   "Question":"The boss of the maze stage, Black Beat Stepper, chooses his attacks by doing what?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Rolling a die",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Flipping a coin",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Spinning a wheel",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Picking a card",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/10/2016 23:56:13",
   "QKEY":"Q78",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Twinge",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy VI (SNES)",
   "Question":"Which of these stats are not actually used for calculations?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Evade %",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Vigor",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Stamina",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mag. Def",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/11/2016 13:14:00",
   "QKEY":"Q79",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"SnoruntPyro",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man IV",
   "Question":"Which one of these Robot Masters is NOT in Mega Man 4?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Gravity Man",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dive Man",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bright Man",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Drill Man",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/11/2016 19:42:12",
   "QKEY":"Q80",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Omtarren",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby Super Star",
   "Question":"Which copy ability does NOT change Kirby's color?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Jet Kirby",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Beam Kirby",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ninja Kirby",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Stone Kirby",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/12/2016 4:52:32",
   "QKEY":"Q81",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Europa Universalis IV",
   "Question":"Where is the Incan Empire formed and located?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Western South America",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Eastern South America",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Central America",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Chain of Pacific Islands",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/12/2016 12:12:30",
   "QKEY":"Q82",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"srsly",
   "GameTitle":"Brain Age: Concentration Training",
   "Question":"What is the name of the disembodied low-poly floating head who cheerfully directs you your brain training?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Dr. Kawashima",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dr. Sakuramachi",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dr. Higashiyama",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Dr. Murakami",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/12/2016 14:08:33",
   "QKEY":"Q83",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"srsly",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy 6",
   "Question":"Named after Luke Skywalker's Red Squadron wingmen from Star Wars, these soldiers accompany Tara into Narshe.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Biggs and Wedge",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Cid and Mog",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ultros and Typhon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Gilgamesh and Grendal",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/12/2016 14:41:29",
   "QKEY":"Q84",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"srsly",
   "GameTitle":"Dr. Mario",
   "Question":"Achieving victory over the viruses in the single player game rewards the player with what bizarre cutscene?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The viruses are sitting in a tree, and get abducted by aliens.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The viruses are flushed down a toilet, and wash out into the ocean.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The viruses are stomped repeatedly into a sidewalk by a foot wearing a sandal.",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The viruses are shot out of a cannon into the sun.",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/12/2016 16:30:36",
   "QKEY":"Q85",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Sonic the Hedgehog (2006)",
   "Question":"What is the name of the human Princess that Sonic totally gets to first base with?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Elise",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Amy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Sally",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Madonna",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/13/2016 23:06:21",
   "QKEY":"Q86",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dr. Topper",
   "GameTitle":"Earthbound/Mother 2",
   "Question":"Which status ailment can a Doctor cure?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Poison",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Incapacitation",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Numbness",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Petrify",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/14/2016 15:41:21",
   "QKEY":"Q87",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Starbird",
   "GameTitle":"Kingdom Hearts",
   "Question":"What is the name of the keyblade Riku gives to Kairi",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Destiny's Embrace",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Oathkeeper",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Way to the Dawn",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sign of Innocence",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/17/2016 21:15:09",
   "QKEY":"Q88",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Mjolna",
   "GameTitle":"Devil May Cry 4 ",
   "Question":"What is the name of the ranged weapon wielded by Trish?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Luce & Ombra",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Ebony & Ivory",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Kalina Ann",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Nightmare-Î³",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/17/2016 21:35:01",
   "QKEY":"Q89",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Sonic Adventure 2",
   "Question":"What was Rouge the Bat's initial name during the game's development?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Nails",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Fang",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Heart",
   "FakeAnswer3":"She had no initial name, it was Rouge the whole time.",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/17/2016 22:21:57",
   "QKEY":"Q90",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"TheGentleChainsaw",
   "GameTitle":"Star Wars Episode I: Racer",
   "Question":"on which planet does the Fire Mountain Rally take place?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Baroonda",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Malastare",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mon Gazza",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tatooine",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/18/2016 14:54:39",
   "QKEY":"Q91",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Ky_",
   "GameTitle":"Earthbound",
   "Question":"Which of these characters DOES NOT join Ness?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Runaway Five",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Pokey",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Jeff",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Paula",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/18/2016 15:45:18",
   "QKEY":"Q92",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Don't Starve: Reign of Giants",
   "Question":"Which Giant appears during the Spring season in the Reign of Giants DLC?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Moose/Goose",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Deerclops",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Bearger",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Dragonfly",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/18/2016 15:53:14",
   "QKEY":"Q93",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Jet Set Radio Future",
   "Question":"Which of the following is not a name for one of the games gangs?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Toy Soliders",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Love Shockers",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Noise Tanks",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Doom Riders",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/18/2016 17:14:54",
   "QKEY":"Q94",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Omnicrom",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy 6",
   "Question":"In the SNES version of the game, which Dance could Mog NOT learn in the World of Ruin",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Water Rondo",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dusk Requiem",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Snowman Jazz",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Wind Song",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/18/2016 17:37:38",
   "QKEY":"Q95",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Omnicrom",
   "GameTitle":"Shin Megami Tensei",
   "Question":"What Demon is created by fusing Rangda and Barong?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Shiva",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Vishnu",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mahakala",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ravana",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/19/2016 9:34:32",
   "QKEY":"Q96",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"JK",
   "GameTitle":"Fallout 2",
   "Question":"As a random encounter the player may come across a Bridgekeeper who asks him questions. What is this scene a reference to?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Monty Python and the Holy Grail",
   "FakeAnswer1":"\"Two Cities\" by Charles Dickens",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Fallout 1",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mad Max 2: The Road Warrior",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/20/2016 20:01:00",
   "QKEY":"Q97",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Chameo Five",
   "GameTitle":"Punch-Out (Series)",
   "Question":"What fighter has been in all three console Punch-Out games?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bald Bull",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Piston Honda",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Glass Joe",
   "FakeAnswer3":"King Hippo",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/22/2016 10:49:42",
   "QKEY":"Q98",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Color Printer",
   "GameTitle":"Castlevania: Symphony of the Night",
   "Question":"Which sub-weapon costs Alucard the most hearts to use?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Cross",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Stopwatch",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Holy Book",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Axe",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/22/2016 12:16:56",
   "QKEY":"Q99",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy IV (SNES)",
   "Question":"This karate master joins you on Mt. Hobs to fight the MomBomb:",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Yang",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Tao",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Yin",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Zen",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/22/2016 18:58:45",
   "QKEY":"Q100",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"FlamingRok",
   "GameTitle":"Pac-Man 2: The New Adventures",
   "Question":"Who is not in Pac-Man's family?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pac-Man's Cat",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Pac-Jr.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Pac-Baby",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pac-Man's Dog",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/23/2016 4:00:51",
   "QKEY":"Q101",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"thevoiceofdog",
   "GameTitle":"Earthbound",
   "Question":"Which food item restores the most hp?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Brain Food Lunch",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hamburger",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bag of Fries",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Cookie",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/23/2016 17:57:17",
   "QKEY":"Q102",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"thevoiceofdog",
   "GameTitle":"Earthbound",
   "Question":"What do the ruler and protractor do when used in battle?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Nothing",
   "FakeAnswer1":"They buff your party",
   "FakeAnswer2":"They confuse the enemy",
   "FakeAnswer3":"They increase chances of item drop after battle",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/24/2016 0:12:22",
   "QKEY":"Q103",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"The Elder Scrolls: Skyrim",
   "Question":"If looking to gather Juniper Berries, which city would you head for?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Markarth",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Solitude",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Morthal",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Falkreath",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/24/2016 16:56:37",
   "QKEY":"Q104",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby 64",
   "Question":"What is the name the fairy that Kirby helps on his quest?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Ribbon",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Pinky",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Adeleine",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tinkerbell ",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/25/2016 3:41:10",
   "QKEY":"Q105",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"The Secret of Monkey Island",
   "Question":"Which item does Guybrush use to reach Hook Isle?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Rubber Chicken with a Pulley in the Middle",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Extra Strong Magnetic Compass",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shovel",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Navigator's Necklace",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/25/2016 14:18:22",
   "QKEY":"Q106",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy Tactics",
   "Question":"What is the only way to light up the maps in Deep Dungeon?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Crystals left by corpses",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lighting torches on specific tiles",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bringing a special item that lights the room",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Casting an illumination spell",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/26/2016 11:38:25",
   "QKEY":"Q107",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"The New Tetris (N64)",
   "Question":"To create a gold square, you need four of the same tetromino put into a 4x4 space. Which piece type CANNOT make a gold square?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The S/Z piece",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The T piece",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The I piece",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The L/J piece",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/28/2016 3:09:55",
   "QKEY":"Q108",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Lock Knight",
   "GameTitle":"Breath of Fire",
   "Question":"Which city faced nightly zombie outbreaks?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Romero",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Carmen",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Gust",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Camlon",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/28/2016 11:51:26",
   "QKEY":"Q109",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Glutenfree",
   "GameTitle":"Wario Land 3 (GBC)",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a status effect/transformation in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Concrete Wario",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Fat Wario",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bouncy Wario",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Vampire Wario",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/28/2016 18:41:02",
   "QKEY":"Q110",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"The Witcher (series)",
   "Question":"The games are based off of the same-titled short-story series by what Polish author?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Andrzej Sapkowski",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Konrad T. Lewandowski",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rafal A. Ziemkiewicz",
   "FakeAnswer3":" William B.J. Blazkowicz",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/28/2016 19:00:41",
   "QKEY":"Q111",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"Myst",
   "Question":"Which of the four ages requires the use of water pumps to power elevators?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Channelwood",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Stoneship",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Selenitic",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mechanical",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"1/31/2016 22:23:24",
   "QKEY":"Q112",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mirror Knight",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby Super Star",
   "Question":"Which of these copy abilities does not appear in the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tornado",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Paint",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Copy",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jet",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/1/2016 14:06:27",
   "QKEY":"Q113",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Tales From The Borderlands",
   "Question":"Which of these previous Vault Hunters (playable characters) does not appear in Tales from the Borderlands?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Salvador",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Athena",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Zer0",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mordecai",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/1/2016 14:41:48",
   "QKEY":"Q114",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Super Amazing Wagon Adventure",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a possible thing you can fight?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Satan",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A satellite",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Velociraptors",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Drug-fueled hallucinations",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/2/2016 3:58:41",
   "QKEY":"Q115",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mjolna",
   "GameTitle":"Huniepop",
   "Question":"Who here isn't a romanceable character in Huniepop?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Mitsuna Youmoto",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Audrey Belrose",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Kyanna Delrio",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Theiatena Venus",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/2/2016 10:57:21",
   "QKEY":"Q116",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Shovel Knight",
   "Question":"Which of these members of the Order of No Quarter does not/will not have their own playable expansion?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Treasure Knight",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Plague Knight",
   "FakeAnswer2":"King Knight",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Spectre Knight",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/5/2016 13:32:13",
   "QKEY":"Q117",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Phantasy Star 4",
   "Question":"What does Chaz's skill \"Earth\" do?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Stuns a single enemy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Deals earth damage to all enemies",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Reduces the speed of a single enemy",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Adds earth element to his attacks",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/5/2016 14:06:13",
   "QKEY":"Q118",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo",
   "Question":"Which of these consoles did not receive a port of Super Street Fighter 2 Turbo?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sega CD",
   "FakeAnswer1":"3DO",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dreamcast",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Playstation 2",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/8/2016 22:12:37",
   "QKEY":"Q119",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"NuclearPotato",
   "GameTitle":"Battle Garrega",
   "Question":"Battle Garrega is notorious for its complex rank system.  Which of the following actions does not increase rank?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Losing a life",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Increasing the autofire rate",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Firing your main weapon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Starting a new game or continuing after a game over",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/13/2016 14:26:16",
   "QKEY":"Q120",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"March of the Eagles",
   "Question":"Which of these nations isn't a \"major\" nation?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Denmark",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Sweden",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Spain",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ottoman Empire",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/17/2016 4:51:07",
   "QKEY":"Q121",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Baloney Amputation",
   "GameTitle":"Suikoden",
   "Question":"Which character can possibly be killed by the main character's father?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pahn",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Gremio",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Luc",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pesmerga",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/21/2016 17:12:31",
   "QKEY":"Q122",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy V",
   "Question":"Near the end of the second act, which party member dies and gets replaced by Krile?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Galuf",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Bartz",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lenna",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Faris",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/22/2016 12:08:21",
   "QKEY":"Q123",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Dark Chronicle/Dark Cloud 2",
   "Question":"Which of these words BEST describes Spheda?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Golf",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Crafting",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Redhead",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Cards",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/22/2016 20:56:39",
   "QKEY":"Q124",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Chameo Five",
   "GameTitle":"Sonic Adventure",
   "Question":"What is the least visited stage in the game? (Hint: Only Sonic and Knuckles can access this stage)",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Lost World",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Red Mountain",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Final Egg",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Hot Shelter",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/22/2016 22:16:15",
   "QKEY":"Q125",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Chameo Five",
   "GameTitle":"Dead Rising 2",
   "Question":"Who is the final boss of the best possible ending path?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tyrone King",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Raymond Sullivan",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dwight Boykin",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Brandon Whittaker",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/25/2016 17:09:23",
   "QKEY":"Q126",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"Fallout",
   "Question":"Which of these characters isn't a Talking Head? (they have voice-acted dialogue, unlike everyone else)",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tycho",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Decker",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Morpheus",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Laura",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/27/2016 1:29:54",
   "QKEY":"Q127",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"City of Heroes",
   "Question":"Which villain group was particularly notorious for having enemies who could sap your energy to disable your powers?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Malta",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Circle of Thorns",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Freakshow",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Council",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/28/2016 20:37:40",
   "QKEY":"Q128",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dan Genesis",
   "GameTitle":"Shining Force II",
   "Question":"Which character has the class \"Red Baron\"?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Lemon",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Sheela",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Jaro",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Rohde",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/28/2016 21:19:01",
   "QKEY":"Q129",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Danganronpa 2: Goodbye Despair",
   "Question":"Which trial minigame involves elements of rhythm action gameplay?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Panic Talk Action",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hangman's Gambit",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rebuttal Showdown",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Logic Dive",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/28/2016 21:49:35",
   "QKEY":"Q130",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"JamieTheD",
   "GameTitle":"Master of Orion 3",
   "Question":"Which *Playable* race in MoO 3 is a mutation of the Trilarians?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Sakkra",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Darlok",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Icthyosians",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Ikthul",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/28/2016 22:05:00",
   "QKEY":"Q131",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Sim City 2000",
   "Question":"Which of the following is not a type of arcology?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Soleri ",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Darco",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Plymouth",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Launch",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/29/2016 19:18:44",
   "QKEY":"Q132",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Chameo Five",
   "GameTitle":"Assassin's Creed (Series)",
   "Question":"Out of these 4, what country has an Assassin's Creed game not taken place in yet?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Spain",
   "FakeAnswer1":"France",
   "FakeAnswer2":"China",
   "FakeAnswer3":"India",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"2/29/2016 23:32:43",
   "QKEY":"Q133",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Borderlands 2",
   "Question":"What is the special property of Tediore guns?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Instead of reloading, you use the gun as a grenade",
   "FakeAnswer1":"They're really, really crappy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"They have increased damage at the expense of accuracy",
   "FakeAnswer3":"They use up multiple bullets per shot",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 13:10:19",
   "QKEY":"Q134",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"LISA: The Painful RPG",
   "Question":"Which party member can you recruit by winning at russian roulette?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Buckets",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Fly Minetti",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mad Dog",
   "FakeAnswer3":"RT",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 13:34:18",
   "QKEY":"Q135",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Fire Emblem Awakening",
   "Question":"What is the name of Sully's daughter?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Kjelle",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Severa",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Noire",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Cynthia",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 15:27:26",
   "QKEY":"Q136",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Advance Wars: Days of Ruin",
   "Question":"Which is the only indirect combat unit that can return fire in combat?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Anti-tank",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Rockets",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Missiles",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Artillery",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 16:15:06",
   "QKEY":"Q137",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Metal Gear Solid 3",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a valid strategy when fighting The End?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tranquillizing his parrot to distract him for a moment, and then punching him",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Using the thermal goggles to follow his footprints",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Using the binoculars to look for the sun reflecting off his scope",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Waiting for a week in real-time so he dies of old age",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 16:51:21",
   "QKEY":"Q138",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Touch My Katamari",
   "Question":"Why does the King of all Cosmos send the Prince to roll stuff up in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"To prove to the people of earth that the King is still the best at everything",
   "FakeAnswer1":"To replace the stars the King destroyed",
   "FakeAnswer2":"To replace the islands the King destroyed with a tsunami",
   "FakeAnswer3":"To attempt to cure the King's amnesia",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 17:22:40",
   "QKEY":"Q139",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Metroid Fusion",
   "Question":"What is the name given to the parasite that impersonates Samus in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"SA-X",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dark Samus",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Samus 2.0",
   "FakeAnswer3":"UAC #998",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 17:51:06",
   "QKEY":"Q140",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Super Meat Boy",
   "Question":"What game is the intro cutscene to World 2 (The Hospital) a reference to?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Castlevania",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Street Fighter II",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shinobi",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mega Man 2",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/1/2016 18:13:57",
   "QKEY":"Q141",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Oddworld: Abe's Oddysee",
   "Question":"In the Playstation version of the game, what is the controller command to make Abe fart?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"L2 + Circle",
   "FakeAnswer1":"L2 + Triangle",
   "FakeAnswer2":"L2 + Square",
   "FakeAnswer3":"L2 + X",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/2/2016 12:50:25",
   "QKEY":"Q142",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Xenoblade Chronicles X",
   "Question":"What is the name of the human-like robots piloted remotely by the humans of New LA?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Mims",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mems",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mimes",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mimics",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/2/2016 14:15:58",
   "QKEY":"Q143",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Sound Shapes",
   "Question":"Which of these is NOT a lyric featured in the album/world \"Cities\", by popular musician Beck?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"They say that we've got nothing/But a dollar for a life of sin",
   "FakeAnswer1":"You weren't made for this place/But it's not your fault",
   "FakeAnswer2":"We will sleep/Widow's web",
   "FakeAnswer3":"We don't care just where we're going/You and i we'll climb so high",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/4/2016 9:17:50",
   "QKEY":"Q144",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Metal Gear Rising: Revengance",
   "Question":"Who initially convinces Jetstream Sam to join up with Senator Armstrong?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Senator Armstrong himself",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Sundowner",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Monsoon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"LQ-84i (aka Blade Wolf)",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/4/2016 22:05:32",
   "QKEY":"Q145",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Roast Grief",
   "GameTitle":"Skies of Arcadia",
   "Question":"What is the name of Drachma's ship?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Little Jack",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Delphinus",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Albatross",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Blackbeard",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 8:14:07",
   "QKEY":"Q146",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"OFF",
   "Question":"What is the fifth and final element, that is manufactured in Zone 3?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sugar",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Plastic",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Meat",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Metal",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 11:35:05",
   "QKEY":"Q147",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"XCOM: Terror From The Deep",
   "Question":"A Commander of which race must be captured to unlock the final mission?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Lobsterman Commander",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Aquatoid Commander",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Gill Man Commander",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tasoth Commander",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 11:56:49",
   "QKEY":"Q148",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"XCOM: Apocalypse",
   "Question":"What is the only UFO Type Micronoid Aggregates can be found in?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Alien Bomber",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Alien Battleship",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Alien Mothership",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Alien Assault Ship",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 20:02:35",
   "QKEY":"Q149",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Loose Snausage",
   "GameTitle":"Wario Land 3",
   "Question":"Which powerup  lets you  fall through platforms? ",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Zombie wario",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Vampire Bat Wario",
   "FakeAnswer2":"String Wario",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Fire wario",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 21:24:16",
   "QKEY":"Q150",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Crotch",
   "GameTitle":"Mutant League Football",
   "Question":"What is the name of the only all-alien team?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Psycho Slashers",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Deathskin Razors",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Sixty Whiners",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Screaming Evils",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 21:46:30",
   "QKEY":"Q151",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Hack 'N' Slash",
   "Question":"What item does you get that allows you access the game's debugging interface?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Third Eye Hat",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Fourth Wall Visor",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Netherworld Goggles",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Insectoid Helm",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 22:15:33",
   "QKEY":"Q152",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Linebeck",
   "GameTitle":"Golgo 13",
   "Question":"What is the pseudonym of Golgo 13?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Duke Togo",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Prince Togo",
   "FakeAnswer2":"King Togo",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Oz Togo",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/6/2016 22:38:59",
   "QKEY":"Q153",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy X-2",
   "Question":"Which ultra-hard to get dressphere do you obtain by getting an \"Episode Complete!\" for every area of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Mascot",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Psychic",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lady Luck",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Trainer",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/7/2016 0:55:30",
   "QKEY":"Q154",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"slowbeef",
   "GameTitle":"Metal Gear Solid (series)",
   "Question":"Given the code names below, which character's real name is George?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Solidus Snake",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Decoy Octopus",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Fear",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Drebin",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/7/2016 1:13:02",
   "QKEY":"Q155",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"slowbeef",
   "GameTitle":"Bloodborne",
   "Question":"What is the item used to heal?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Blood Vials",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Estus Flasks",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lifegems",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Crescent Herb Grass",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/8/2016 0:05:56",
   "QKEY":"Q156",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mjolna",
   "GameTitle":"Ghosts N' Goblins",
   "Question":"Which weapon is necessary to beat the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Cross/Shield",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dagger",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lance",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Crossbow",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/9/2016 21:16:59",
   "QKEY":"Q157",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"The Talos Principle",
   "Question":"What is the name of the computer library assistant that debates you throughout the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Milton",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Morton",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Murton",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Martin",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/10/2016 22:01:17",
   "QKEY":"Q158",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Saturn",
   "GameTitle":"Zero Escape: Nine Hours, Nine Persons, Nine Doors ",
   "Question":"The character with a bracelet value of 2 has a few names/nicknames. Which of the following is not one of them?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Twain",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Prince",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Snake",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Light",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/13/2016 20:23:24",
   "QKEY":"Q159",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Solar Eclipse",
   "Question":"What is the callsign of the protagonist?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Stuntman",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hellcat",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Vegas",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Phantom",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/13/2016 21:01:33",
   "QKEY":"Q160",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"zetwo",
   "GameTitle":"Baten Kaitos Orgins",
   "Question":"What  is the name of the dark god inside Sagi?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"malpercio",
   "FakeAnswer1":"sever",
   "FakeAnswer2":"crynax",
   "FakeAnswer3":"(what ever you named him)",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/14/2016 4:01:01",
   "QKEY":"Q161",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"NeoTM",
   "GameTitle":"Defender (1981)",
   "Question":"What is the name of the weapon that clears every enemy on the screen?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Smart Bomb",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mutant Blaster",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Super Mine",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Orbital Missile",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/14/2016 4:11:00",
   "QKEY":"Q162",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"NeoTM",
   "GameTitle":"Star Fox Adventures",
   "Question":"What is the name of Fox's dinosaur sidekick?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tricky",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dino",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rolly",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Burns",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/14/2016 4:31:28",
   "QKEY":"Q163",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"NeoTM",
   "GameTitle":"Half Life 2",
   "Question":"In which stage do you first pick up the Gravity Gun?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Black Mesa East",
   "FakeAnswer1":"We Don't Go to Ravenholm...",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Nova Prospekt",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Entanglement",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/14/2016 19:30:58",
   "QKEY":"Q164",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Gnoll Queen",
   "GameTitle":"TES: Daggerfall",
   "Question":"Despite all the lore telling us that she was a dark elf, Queen Barenziah had the sprite of a?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Breton",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Orc",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Khajiit",
   "FakeAnswer3":"High Elf",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/15/2016 23:31:58",
   "QKEY":"Q165",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Spyro 3: Year Of The Dragon",
   "Question":"Which of the following stages does not have a sub level for Sgt. Byrd",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Seashell Shore",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Molten Crater",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Enchanted Towers",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Charmed Ridge",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/16/2016 6:31:19",
   "QKEY":"Q166",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Dragon Warrior Monsters",
   "Question":"Darkdrium, the most powerful monster in the game, is a recolor of what other monster?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Durran",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Zoma",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dracolord",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Servant",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/17/2016 8:52:29",
   "QKEY":"Q167",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Zanzibar Ham",
   "GameTitle":"Hero Core",
   "Question":"Who composed the game's soundtrack?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Brother Android",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Daniel Remar",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Disasterpeace",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Chris Geehan",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/19/2016 18:22:25",
   "QKEY":"Q168",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Sephohmahark",
   "GameTitle":"Fire Emblem: The Sacred Stones",
   "Question":"Which of the following isn't the ability of a class skill?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Attack five times consecutively at half damage",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Ignore enemy DEF for one attack",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Prevent all damage from one attack",
   "FakeAnswer3":"One-hit kill",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 10:25:41",
   "QKEY":"Q169",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"basedsekibanki",
   "GameTitle":"The Binding of Isaac: Afterbirth",
   "Question":"Out of all the items listed here, which item as of Afterbirth is not a 'special' item?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Stopwatch",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dr. Fetus",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Godhead",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pyromaniac",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 19:33:42",
   "QKEY":"Q170",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Elite Beat Agents",
   "Question":"What song plays during the mission where a taxi driver is trying to get a pregnant woman to the hospital?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sk8er Boi - Avril Lavigne",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Survivor - Destiny's Child",
   "FakeAnswer2":"YMCA - The Village People",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Just Dance - Jamiroquai",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 20:42:02",
   "QKEY":"Q171",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Iron Brigade",
   "Question":"Which of the following is not a type of monovision?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Freddy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Arty",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Big Willie",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tommy",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 21:17:38",
   "QKEY":"Q172",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"yomidian",
   "GameTitle":"Ys Origin",
   "Question":"What material is used to upgrade the player character's weapons?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Cleria Ore",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mythril Nugget",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Orichalcum Orb",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Zemurian Stone",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 21:34:33",
   "QKEY":"Q173",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Freedom Force",
   "Question":"Which is not a superhero featured in the first Freedom Force game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Shadow",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Minuteman",
   "FakeAnswer2":"El Diablo",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bullet",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 21:38:23",
   "QKEY":"Q174",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Plants Vs. Zombies",
   "Question":"What plant costs the most to buy from Crazy Dave's Twiddydinkies?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Imitater",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Cob Cannon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Gold Magnet",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Gattling Pea",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/20/2016 22:13:52",
   "QKEY":"Q175",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Super Mario 64",
   "Question":"The Chuckya, purple enemies resembling bo-bombs, are NOT found in which of these stages?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Hazy Maze Cave",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Tiny-Huge Island",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rainbow Ride",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Wet-Dry World",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/21/2016 7:04:53",
   "QKEY":"Q176",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Future Cop: LAPD",
   "Question":"What genre is the gameplay mode, \"Precinct Assault\"?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A MOBA",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A tower defence game",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A racing game",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A top down shmup",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/22/2016 2:44:48",
   "QKEY":"Q177",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Crotch",
   "GameTitle":"The Secret of Monkey Island",
   "Question":"What is the only way to die?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Stay underwater for ten minutes.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Shoot yourself with a cannon.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Steal from the voodoo lady.",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Get caught by LeChuck's crew.",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/22/2016 18:56:47",
   "QKEY":"Q178",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Megaman X7",
   "Question":"What does the Head armor do?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Increased Item Pickup Range",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Passive Health Regeneration",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Special Weapons ammo consumption is halved",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Store Up to 4 Charge Shots.",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/23/2016 13:04:51",
   "QKEY":"Q179",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Zanzibar Ham",
   "GameTitle":"Hero Core",
   "Question":"Which previous Daniel Remar game is heavily referenced in this game's Annihilation mode?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Iji",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hyper Princess Pitch",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Garden Gnome Carnage",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Lyle in Cube Sector",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/23/2016 21:44:22",
   "QKEY":"Q180",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mercury Knuckle",
   "GameTitle":"Civilization",
   "Question":"Which one of these civilizations did not appear in the original Sid Meier's Civilization (1991)?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Japanese",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Russians",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Americans",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Mongols",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/26/2016 2:52:44",
   "QKEY":"Q181",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"DoctorNovakaine",
   "GameTitle":"Lufia 2",
   "Question":"Maxim is unable to learn spells of which element?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Fire",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Thunder",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Water",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Ice",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/27/2016 0:00:18",
   "QKEY":"Q182",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Frankomatic",
   "GameTitle":"Kid Niki",
   "Question":"What does the scroll say in the intro cutscene as the Radical Ninja busts through the wall of his dojo?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"WILL HELP YOU!",
   "FakeAnswer1":"I'LL HELP YOU!",
   "FakeAnswer2":"WILL SAVE YOU!",
   "FakeAnswer3":"BELIEVE IT!",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/27/2016 13:56:47",
   "QKEY":"Q183",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Doom",
   "Question":"Which of these isn't a difficulty setting in the original PC Doom?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"I am a wimp",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hurt me plenty",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Hey, not too rough",
   "FakeAnswer3":"I'm too young to die",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/27/2016 14:25:27",
   "QKEY":"Q184",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Soul Calibur III",
   "Question":"What unusual weapon does Tira use?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A large, hula-hoop like blade, with a dull inside and sharp outside",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A set of nunchaku, but with a third bar instead of a connecting chain",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A floating orb, which she controls with her mind",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A sword with three blades, spread 120 degrees apart",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/27/2016 19:35:24",
   "QKEY":"Q185",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Nuclear Throne",
   "Question":"Y.V. stands for...",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Yung Venuz",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Your Veriness",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Yakob Venarius",
   "FakeAnswer3":"It doesn't actually stand for anything...",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/28/2016 18:17:51",
   "QKEY":"Q186",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Perfect Dark",
   "Question":"Name the weapon that can fire 'fly-by-wire' rockets as its' alternate fire mode.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Slayer",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dragon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Reaper",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Devastator",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/28/2016 21:12:45",
   "QKEY":"Q187",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Hotel Dusk: Room 215",
   "Question":"What is the name of the ex-partner that Kyle has been hunting?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bradley",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Benjamin",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Brian",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Brandon",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/30/2016 6:46:17",
   "QKEY":"Q188",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Warioware: Twisted!",
   "Question":"Which character's microgame collection features a microgame where a man shoots his hands at flying noses?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Kat & Ana",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wario-Man",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mona",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jimmy T",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/30/2016 14:25:28",
   "QKEY":"Q189",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Pokemon",
   "Question":"Which of these Pokemon changed type in the transition from gen 1 (Red & Blue) to gen 2 (Gold & Silver)?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Magnemite",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Voltorb",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Onix",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Gengar",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/31/2016 4:00:05",
   "QKEY":"Q190",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"TackyRackyor0dd1",
   "GameTitle":"Fantasy Zone",
   "Question":"Long before Sonic the Hedgehog existed, this game's protagonist was considered to be one of SEGA's first mascot characters.  What is this character's name?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Opa-Opa",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mr. Fantasy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Alex Kidd",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Puyo",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"3/31/2016 15:39:19",
   "QKEY":"Q191",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo-Kazooie",
   "Question":"From Grunty's Furnace Fun: In Mumbo's Mountain you don't know, what does that big gorilla throw?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Oranges",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Chocolates",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Barrels",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Banana Peels",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/1/2016 2:33:05",
   "QKEY":"Q192",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo-Kazooie",
   "Question":"From Grunty's Furnace Fun: The giant plant in Click Clock Wood, How does it get water for its bud?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"From a camel",
   "FakeAnswer1":"From a giant watering can",
   "FakeAnswer2":"From Kazooieâ€™s special water eggs",
   "FakeAnswer3":"From Mumbo's rain dance",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/1/2016 2:37:37",
   "QKEY":"Q193",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo-Kazooie",
   "Question":"From Grunty's Furnace Fun: Get this wrong, make a mistake, which color Jinjo is a fake?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Brown",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Yellow",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Green",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Purple",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/3/2016 4:00:53",
   "QKEY":"Q194",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Small bird",
   "GameTitle":"E.V.O. Search for Eden",
   "Question":"What body parts are required to start evolving into a human?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Rabbit Body and Cat Jaws",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lemur Body and Baboon Jaws",
   "FakeAnswer2":" Rhinoceros Body and Fierce Jaws",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mermaid Body and Mermaid Jaws",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/3/2016 17:22:04",
   "QKEY":"Q195",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Pokemon Trading Card Game (GBC)",
   "Question":"The Set of Legendary Pokemon cards contains what In addition to the elemental birds?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Dragonite",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mew",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mewtwo",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Lapras",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/3/2016 20:02:52",
   "QKEY":"Q196",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"greendayrock92",
   "GameTitle":"Spider-Man and Venom: Maximum Carnage",
   "Question":"Which classic rock song was featured on the game's soundtrack?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Mob Rules",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Thunderstruck",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Living on a Prayer",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Smells Like Teen Spirit",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/3/2016 21:17:42",
   "QKEY":"Q197",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Ace Attorney Investigations: Miles Edgeworth",
   "Question":"In \"Turnabout Airlines\", what is the killer's motive for murder?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"To hide their involvement in a smuggling ring",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Jealousy at having been passed up for promotion",
   "FakeAnswer2":"To try and frame Edgeworth due to a grudge",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Self defence - they were assaulted with a gun",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/3/2016 21:53:36",
   "QKEY":"Q198",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Batman: Return of the Joker (Game Boy)",
   "Question":"Who is the boss fought on top of a train car at the end of the train stage?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Foul Ball",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dark Claw",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shogun Warrior",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Joker",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/5/2016 6:25:48",
   "QKEY":"Q199",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Darkwing Duck (NES)",
   "Question":"Which villian is fought at the \"warehouse\"?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Megavolt",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wolfduck",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Liquidator",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Steelbeak",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/5/2016 6:51:00",
   "QKEY":"Q200",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy I",
   "Question":"Chaos knows several special spells that you never see elsewhere in the game. Which of these is one of them?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Crack",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wave",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Spiral",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Crash",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/5/2016 11:53:01",
   "QKEY":"Q201",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"Lego Racers",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a racer you are up against in the 1st Circuit Race?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sam Sinister",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Ann Droid",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rob-N-Hood",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Captain Redbeard",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/5/2016 22:35:19",
   "QKEY":"Q202",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Chameo Five",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo-Kazooie",
   "Question":"In what stage does Mr. Vile challenge you to eat more Grumblies than him after Banjo transforms into a crocodile?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bubblegloop Swamp",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Click Clock Wood",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rusty Bucket Bay",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Clanker's Cavern",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/7/2016 3:25:50",
   "QKEY":"Q203",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"The Witcher (PC)",
   "Question":"Which of these common monsters does not make an appearance in the first Witcher game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Nekkers",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Drowners",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Alghouls",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Wyvern",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/9/2016 18:21:09",
   "QKEY":"Q204",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Minosheep",
   "GameTitle":"Azure Dreams",
   "Question":"Which of the following women can't be courted?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Weedy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Nico",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Selfie",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Cherrl",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/10/2016 19:51:13",
   "QKEY":"Q205",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Frankomatic",
   "GameTitle":"Blake Stone: Aliens of Gold",
   "Question":"Star Troopers sometimes fake their death after taking damage. What do they yell when playing dead instead of actually dying?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"I'm down!",
   "FakeAnswer1":"I'm hit!",
   "FakeAnswer2":"You got me!",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Medic!",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/10/2016 21:18:26",
   "QKEY":"Q206",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"XenobladeMonicals",
   "GameTitle":"Jade Empire: Special Edition",
   "Question":"What is the name of the first gem you obtain?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Flawed Warrior Gem",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Flawed Monk Gem",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Flawed Scholar Gem",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Warrior's Gem of Forethought",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/10/2016 21:35:19",
   "QKEY":"Q207",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"XenobladeMonicals",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy XII",
   "Question":"In FFXII, who is Gilgamesh voiced by?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"John DiMaggio",
   "FakeAnswer1":"James Earl Jones",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Morgan Freeman",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Billy West",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/10/2016 21:59:57",
   "QKEY":"Q208",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Metal Gear Rising: Revengance",
   "Question":"Complete the song lyric: \"And they run when the sun comes up/With their lives on the line (Alive!)...\"",
   "CorrectAnswer":"For a while (No choice!)",
   "FakeAnswer1":"RULES OF NATURE!!",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Yeah â€“ this is what nature planned",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Which of them will succeed, strong or weak",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/10/2016 22:07:18",
   "QKEY":"Q209",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Verrilous",
   "GameTitle":"Fire Emblem: Fates",
   "Question":"Which of the following characters is NOT playable in the Conquest route?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Scarlet",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Izana",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shura",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Flora",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/10/2016 22:27:14",
   "QKEY":"Q210",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Diamond",
   "GameTitle":"Super Robot Wars",
   "Question":"Which of the following franchises was not present in the original Super Robot Wars game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Macross",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Gundam",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Mazinger Z",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Getter Robo",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/11/2016 12:13:45",
   "QKEY":"Q211",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Psychedelic Eyeball",
   "GameTitle":"Doom",
   "Question":"What monster am I? I'm pink, I run pretty fast and I'm the only monster who doesn't have a ranged attack.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Demon",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Imp",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Specter",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Cacodemon",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/12/2016 17:57:52",
   "QKEY":"Q212",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MKcyborg",
   "GameTitle":"Pop'n Music Ã©clale",
   "Question":"Which of these anime openings was NOT introduced as a playable song in PnM Ã©clale? ",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Let Me Hear (Parasyte -The Maxim- ",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Reclimb (Yowamushi Pedal)",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Kakushinteki metamaruphose! (Himouto! Umaru-chan)",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mazeruna kiken (Ushio to Tora)",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/12/2016 20:49:52",
   "QKEY":"Q213",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"johnny longtorso",
   "GameTitle":"Dragon Warrior II",
   "Question":"What kind of animal did the evil sorceror Hargon transform the Princess of Moonbrooke into?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"a dog",
   "FakeAnswer1":"a cat",
   "FakeAnswer2":"a horse",
   "FakeAnswer3":"a slime",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/13/2016 16:43:17",
   "QKEY":"Q214",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Tales of Vesperia",
   "Question":"Which of the following is not one of Rita's casting inantations?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"O' celestial voyagers faster and brighter then the gods, rain down and purify these wreched souls!",
   "FakeAnswer1":"O' mad and greedy waters, rise up and storm the very heavens!",
   "FakeAnswer2":"O' disturbing power now unleashed, mete thy judgment upon the evil before me!",
   "FakeAnswer3":"O' seething fire, be as a holy beast to devour the wicked!",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/14/2016 3:10:40",
   "QKEY":"Q215",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Zerochan",
   "GameTitle":"Sonic 2",
   "Question":"Which of these levels was never planned for inclusion in Sonic 2 at any point in development?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Fire Rise Zone",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wood Zone",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Genocide City Zone",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Hidden Palace Zone",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/14/2016 14:09:20",
   "QKEY":"Q216",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"FinalGamer",
   "GameTitle":"The DIG",
   "Question":"What was the nickname for the \"asteroid\" at the start of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Attila",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hannibal",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Genghis Khan",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Alexander",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/16/2016 16:43:53",
   "QKEY":"Q217",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Ragny",
   "GameTitle":"Roundabout",
   "Question":"What is the name of the skeleton?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Jeffrey",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Georgio",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Beth",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mickey",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/17/2016 6:41:05",
   "QKEY":"Q218",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Shadow the Hedgehog",
   "Question":"Which of the following statements about Shadow the Hedgehog is false?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Shadow, post Sonic Adventure 2, is an android created to mimic the deceased original",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Shadow is over 50 years old",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shadow was created as part of research to cure the autoimmune disease N.I.D.S.",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Shadow was created with the blood of the alien Black Doom",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/17/2016 17:30:21",
   "QKEY":"Q219",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Babycowland",
   "GameTitle":"Style Savvy: Trendsetters",
   "Question":"Which of the following is not a taste/style in Style Savvy: Trendsetters?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Punk",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Gothic",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Pop",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Flirty",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/17/2016 20:35:57",
   "QKEY":"Q220",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Rurfs",
   "GameTitle":"PokÃ©mon Generation 2",
   "Question":"Which two Generation 1 PokÃ©mon had their types adjusted when the Dark and Steel types were added?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Magnemite and Magneton",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Onix and Steelix",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Haunter and Gengar",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Drowzee and Hypno",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/17/2016 20:57:44",
   "QKEY":"Q221",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"G1ganator",
   "GameTitle":"Megaman battle network 2",
   "Question":"when you are prepering to leave netopia lan can buy each of his friends a presant, a broach for mayl a goldring for yai and what for dex",
   "CorrectAnswer":"RoboX",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Gigantor",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ray mk ii",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Gundam!!!",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/17/2016 21:33:36",
   "QKEY":"Q222",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man X6",
   "Question":"In which Maverick's stage do you fight Nightmare Zero?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Infinity Mijinion",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Metal Shark Player",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Blaze Heatnix",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Commander Yammark",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/17/2016 22:06:07",
   "QKEY":"Q223",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Caestars",
   "GameTitle":"Ensemble Stars",
   "Question":"Which is not a stat?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Appeal",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Dance",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Vocal",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Performance",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/18/2016 23:10:32",
   "QKEY":"Q224",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Solar Flair",
   "GameTitle":"Illusion Of Gaia",
   "Question":"In the Incan Ruins how do you solve the Gold Room's puzzle?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Play a song and stand still on specific spot for awhile",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Defeat all enemies in the room",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Scratch the paint off the fake gold and reveal the door there",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Place the Incan Statues in the correct order and then play a song",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/19/2016 0:00:15",
   "QKEY":"Q225",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Solar Flair",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy Tactics Advanced",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a bully from the start of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Patrick",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lyle",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Colin",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Guinness",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/19/2016 5:51:21",
   "QKEY":"Q226",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Morholt",
   "GameTitle":"Pillars of Eternity",
   "Question":"Which follower's quest can be finished before Act II?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Kana",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Sagani",
   "FakeAnswer2":"EdÃ©r",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Durance",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/20/2016 17:23:11",
   "QKEY":"Q227",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 2",
   "Question":"What trick was first introduced to the series in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A Manual",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Burnquist's Racket Air",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Nosegrind",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Tony's Sack Tap",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/21/2016 6:21:18",
   "QKEY":"Q228",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Murlin",
   "GameTitle":"Golden Sun: The Lost Age",
   "Question":"Which of these is NOT one of Star Magician's minions?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Frost Ball",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Guardian Ball",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Thunder Ball",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Anger Ball",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/21/2016 22:03:47",
   "QKEY":"Q229",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Poutine Man",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy X",
   "Question":"Which of these is not the name of a Celestial Weapon?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Ultima",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Caladbolg",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Nirvana",
   "FakeAnswer3":"World Champion",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/22/2016 12:22:15",
   "QKEY":"Q230",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Caestars",
   "GameTitle":"Love Live! School Idol Festival",
   "Question":"What was Î¼'s first single?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bokura no LIVE Kimi to no LIFE",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Snow halation",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Yuujou No Change",
   "FakeAnswer3":"baby maybe Koi no Button",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/23/2016 17:19:02",
   "QKEY":"Q231",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"ManicVolcanic",
   "GameTitle":"Octodad: Dadliest Catch",
   "Question":"What is Octodad's wife's name?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Scarlet",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Stacy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Sally",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sunny",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/24/2016 2:16:46",
   "QKEY":"Q232",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Ratchet and Clank: Going Commando",
   "Question":"Which of the following weapons from the first game is not in Going Commando?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pyrocitor ",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Visibomb Gun",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tesla Claw",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bomb Glove",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/24/2016 22:12:50",
   "QKEY":"Q233",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"The Walking Dead: Season 2",
   "Question":"Why is Clementine forced to sleep in the shed after first meeting the group?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"She was bitten by a dog",
   "FakeAnswer1":"They saw her kill a bandit",
   "FakeAnswer2":"They make all strangers stay in the shed",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The house was full",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/24/2016 22:24:09",
   "QKEY":"Q234",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Rainbow Islands",
   "Question":"Which of these Taito series has an island based around it?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Arkanoid",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Space Invaders",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Elevator Action",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Qix",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/26/2016 8:40:36",
   "QKEY":"Q235",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MattTheSpratt",
   "GameTitle":"Gaming History",
   "Question":"Pong is considered by many people to be the first video arcade game; these people are wrong - what is actually the first arcade game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Computer Space",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Space Invaders",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Gotcha!",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Datsun 280 ZOOM",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/26/2016 14:33:42",
   "QKEY":"Q236",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Caestars",
   "GameTitle":"Love Live! School Idol Festival",
   "Question":"Which girl was a UR in both the Christmas and December sets?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Eli",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Nozomi",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Hanayo",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Honoka",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/26/2016 18:34:49",
   "QKEY":"Q237",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Chrono Trigger",
   "Question":"Which of these Black Omen monsters will give you a Speed Tab if you charm it with Ayla?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Panel",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Martello",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Goon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Synchrite",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/27/2016 1:35:02",
   "QKEY":"Q238",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Sonic & Sega All Stars Racing (Wii)",
   "Question":"DeviantArt of a character from the Sonic the Hedgehog cartoons appears on a playing card in this version of the game. Which character is it?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sonia",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Sally Acorn",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dulcy the Dragon",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Breezie",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"4/27/2016 1:52:27",
   "QKEY":"Q239",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Pokemon (series)",
   "Question":"Which title was the first in the series to include a female playable character?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pokemon Crystal",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Pokemon Trading Card Game",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Pokemon Ruby/Sapphire",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pokemon Stadium",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 14:29:02",
   "QKEY":"Q240",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Football Manager",
   "Question":"What country's league isn't included in any Football Manager game because of licensing issues?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Japan (J-League)",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Netherlands (Eredivisie)",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Chile (Primera DivisiÃ³n)",
   "FakeAnswer3":"United States (Major League Soccer)",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 15:09:21",
   "QKEY":"Q241",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Poutine Man",
   "GameTitle":"The SpongeBob SquarePants Movie",
   "Question":"Which of these is an object SpongeBob uses?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A bowling ball",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A gun",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A lollipop",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A lampshade",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 20:15:41",
   "QKEY":"Q242",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Duke Nukem 3D (PC)",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a skill level in Duke Nukem 3D?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Always Bet On Duke",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Piece Of Cake",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Let's Rock",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Damn I'm Good",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 20:52:57",
   "QKEY":"Q243",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Blaster Master",
   "Question":"Which one of these is NOT an upgrade in Blaster Master?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Spike",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wall 2",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Hover",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Crusher",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 21:06:04",
   "QKEY":"Q244",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Maniac Mansion",
   "Question":"What is Jeff's ability?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Phone Repair",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Microwaving Hamsters",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Developing Film",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jeff doesn't have an ability.",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 21:17:35",
   "QKEY":"Q245",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"A Nightmare On Elm Street",
   "Question":"Which one of these is NOT a Dream Warrior ability?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Punk Rocker",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Necromancer",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shadow Warrior",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Athlete",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 21:22:14",
   "QKEY":"Q246",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo-Kazooie",
   "Question":"Which classic Nintendo console does Banjo play on the file select screen?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Game Boy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Famicom Disk System",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Nintendo 64",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Game and Watch",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 22:00:26",
   "QKEY":"Q247",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Odin Sphere",
   "Question":"What does Mercedes' Psypher weapon resemble?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A crossbow",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A morning star",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A spear",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A sword",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 22:28:07",
   "QKEY":"Q248",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"LooseSnausage",
   "GameTitle":"Video Game History",
   "Question":"What game was created just for the sake of controversy?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Hatred",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Gta Series",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tomb Raider",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Paper Mario and the thousand year door",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 22:51:29",
   "QKEY":"Q249",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Sony/Nintendo",
   "Question":"What was the name of the system the Sony and Nintendo collaborated on?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Nintendo Play Station ",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Nintendo Master System",
   "FakeAnswer2":"CD-i",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sony Stardust",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/22/2016 23:59:04",
   "QKEY":"Q250",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"buri-chan",
   "GameTitle":"Sam and Max (series)",
   "Question":"What does Max refer to himself as?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A lagomorph",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A bunny",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A rabbit",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A rodent",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/23/2016 0:07:03",
   "QKEY":"Q251",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Touhou 7 - Perfect Cherry Blossom ",
   "Question":"This game is the only one in the series to feature what?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A second extra postgame stage",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A male character ",
   "FakeAnswer2":"An official release outside Japan",
   "FakeAnswer3":"\"Focus\" mode that displays your hitbox",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/23/2016 1:53:29",
   "QKEY":"Q252",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Warcraft",
   "Question":"Which of these isn't one of the Eredar Lords of the Burning Legion?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Sargeras",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Kil'jaedan",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Archimonde",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jaraxxus",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 0:31:35",
   "QKEY":"Q253",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Touhou Project (series)",
   "Question":"What is the name of the fantasy land all the games take place in?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Gensokyo",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wonderland",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Pandemonium",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Meikai",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 0:46:31",
   "QKEY":"Q254",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy IX",
   "Question":"The names of the jester characters are what? What are the names of the jester characters?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Zorn & Thorn",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Gemmi & Nye",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Palom & Porom",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Vivi & Zizi",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 0:53:41",
   "QKEY":"Q255",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Ratchet And Clank: Going Commando",
   "Question":"What is not a reward for completing the Megacorp Games Impossible Challenge?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A Platinum Bolt",
   "FakeAnswer1":"200,000 Bolts",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Skill Point",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Snowman Ratchet Skin",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 1:01:38",
   "QKEY":"Q256",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Pokemon Trading Card Game (GB)",
   "Question":"Which of these Trainer Cards was also the name of an NPC in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Imakuni?",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Professor Oak",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Imposter Professor Oak",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mr. Fuji",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 1:08:55",
   "QKEY":"Q257",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Bulletstorm",
   "Question":"What is the password to General Serrano's DNA Bomb?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"URADUMBTIT",
   "FakeAnswer1":"SERRANORULES",
   "FakeAnswer2":"ILIKEBOOBS",
   "FakeAnswer3":"FUCKDEADECHO",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 12:30:25",
   "QKEY":"Q258",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Clock Tower 3",
   "Question":"Which one of these is NOT a Subordinate?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Mutilator",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Corroder",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Chopper",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Scissorwoman",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 12:36:06",
   "QKEY":"Q259",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man Unlimited",
   "Question":"In this Mega Man fan game, what does Yoku Man hate the most?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Rush",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Illusions",
   "FakeAnswer2":"E-Tanks",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Raocow",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 12:48:27",
   "QKEY":"Q260",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Dragon Warrior Monsters",
   "Question":"If you breed a SlimeNite with a BattleRex, the SlimeNite being the Pedigree, what do you get?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"SlimeBorg",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Drakslime",
   "FakeAnswer2":"DragonKid",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Nothing; you cannot breed Slimes and Dragons together.",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 12:57:45",
   "QKEY":"Q261",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Beavis and Butt-Head",
   "Question":"What is the goal of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"See GWAR live.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Whack it in Anderson's shed.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Take a dump at the Mall.",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Turn the game off and do something productive.",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 13:54:51",
   "QKEY":"Q262",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Arthur",
   "GameTitle":"Xenoblade Chronicles X",
   "Question":"The tyrant, Dadaan, the Strongest Prone, has one of these abilities:",
   "CorrectAnswer":"He can destroy all of your party's Skells in one hit",
   "FakeAnswer1":"He has Spike damage",
   "FakeAnswer2":"He can summon a Skell of his own",
   "FakeAnswer3":"He self-destructs at low health",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/24/2016 14:34:24",
   "QKEY":"Q263",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Skunkrocker",
   "GameTitle":"Worms Armaggedon",
   "Question":"What is \"Shopper Mode\"?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"You must collect a crate before you can attack.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Items cost money to use.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Crates never stop spawning.",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Stupid bird!",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/25/2016 1:33:45",
   "QKEY":"Q264",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Overwatch",
   "Question":"Complete the quote: ________ Rains from above.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Justice",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Death",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Missiles",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Victory",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/25/2016 1:42:09",
   "QKEY":"Q265",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Yugioh Forbidden Memories",
   "Question":"Which of the following opponents does not have Gate Guardians in their deck?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Darknite",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Seto 3",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Heishin 2",
   "FakeAnswer3":"High Mage Kepura",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/26/2016 18:51:18",
   "QKEY":"Q266",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby Super Star",
   "Question":"When using the Stone ability, there is a very rare chance Kirby can turn into a statue of ______.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Samus",
   "FakeAnswer1":"King Dedede",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Yoshi",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Donkey Kong",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/27/2016 10:35:12",
   "QKEY":"Q267",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Strong Bad's Cool Game for Attractive People",
   "Question":"What is the name of the race that Strong Bad competes in with Homestar Runner in Episode 1?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Race to the End of the Race",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Free Country USA Marathon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Runner's Run",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The 100 Yards Dash",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/27/2016 12:35:29",
   "QKEY":"Q268",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"FinalGamer",
   "GameTitle":"Broken Sword: Shadow of the Templars",
   "Question":"In Ireland, a man called Sean Fitzgerald is murdered brutally by what means?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Run over by a car",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Attacked by a goat",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shot in the head",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pushed off a cliff",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/27/2016 18:08:27",
   "QKEY":"Q269",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Solar Flair",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man (Series)",
   "Question":"What is the name of Bass's dog?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Trebble",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Woofer",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dash",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Amp",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/27/2016 18:55:13",
   "QKEY":"Q270",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Solar Flair",
   "GameTitle":"Banjo Kazooie",
   "Question":"What other Diddy Kong Racing character appears in Banjo Kazooie?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tiptup",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Pipsy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Tricky",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bumper",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/27/2016 22:00:41",
   "QKEY":"Q271",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Bluhman",
   "GameTitle":"The Witcher 3",
   "Question":"What special trait does the \"Poor Fucking Infantry\" Gwent card carry?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Doubles in strength with each extra card played",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Deals out all other cards in your deck with the same name",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Can be played as either melee or ranged",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Increases strength of all cards in its row by 1",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/27/2016 22:59:54",
   "QKEY":"Q272",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Staghorn",
   "GameTitle":"Crypt of the Necrodancer",
   "Question":"Which of these composers didn't compose a soundtrack for this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Jukio \"Kozilek\" Kallio",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Danny Baranowsky",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Jake Kaufman",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jules Conroy",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/29/2016 4:15:54",
   "QKEY":"Q273",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Tymestalker",
   "GameTitle":"Adventures in the Magic Kingdom",
   "Question":"In the Haunted Mansion ride, if you get hit by the ghost on the first screen, who shows up to tell you 'You'll have to try again'?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The ghost",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mickey",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Donald",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Goofy",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/29/2016 22:43:37",
   "QKEY":"Q274",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Megaman V (Gameboy)",
   "Question":"Which of the bosses based on the outer planets is fought in the first set of Robot Masters?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Neptune",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Uranus",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Saturn",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pluto",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/29/2016 23:24:22",
   "QKEY":"Q275",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Aipom14",
   "GameTitle":"Graffiti Kingdom",
   "Question":"Which of these Taito characters does not cameo as a Super Rare Graffiti?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Tiki (The NewZealand Story)",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Space Invader (Space Invaders)",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bubble Dragons (Bubble Bobble)",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Chuck (Chack'n Pop)",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/30/2016 17:11:19",
   "QKEY":"Q276",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Tymestalker",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy VI",
   "Question":"You can get two Espers by bidding on them in the Auction House.  One is Golem.  What is the other?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Zoneseek",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Fenrir",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Unicorm",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Sraphim",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/30/2016 17:33:31",
   "QKEY":"Q277",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Tymestalker",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy VI",
   "Question":"Which of these is NOT one of Strago's Lores?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Fire Dance",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Aqua Rake",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Pearl Wind",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Step Mine",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/30/2016 17:44:58",
   "QKEY":"Q278",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Tymestalker",
   "GameTitle":"Breath of Fire",
   "Question":"Which item deals 30 damage to each opponent and may only be used once per round?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"E. Key",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Tablet",
   "FakeAnswer2":"LtKey",
   "FakeAnswer3":"KngKey",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"5/30/2016 18:16:37",
   "QKEY":"Q279",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Tymestalker",
   "GameTitle":"Secret of Evermore",
   "Question":"What are the names of the four realms in Evermore?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Prehistoria, Antiqua, Gothica, Omnitopia",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Bugmuck, Nobilia, Ivor Tower, Megaplex",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ankor Wat, Freejia, Oakton, Watermia",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Potos, Kippo, Matango, Kakkara",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/1/2016 19:03:32",
   "QKEY":"Q280",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Megaman 3 DOS",
   "Question":"Which of these robot masters has not had their name reused for another Robot Master or NetNavi?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bit Man",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Shark Man",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Torch Man",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Oil Man",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/2/2016 16:35:42",
   "QKEY":"Q281",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Ratchet and Clank: Going Commando",
   "Question":"What product is Captain Quark testing for Megacorp in the post credits scene?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Crotchetizer",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Quantum Demolecularizer",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Interrogator",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Pain Beam",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 7:27:51",
   "QKEY":"Q282",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Chameleon Twist",
   "Question":"Which of these is not the name of a Chameleon in the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Susan",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Linda",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Jack",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Fred",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 7:39:46",
   "QKEY":"Q283",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Overwatch",
   "Question":"Which is the oldest character in the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Reinhardt",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Torbjorn",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Zenyatta",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bastion",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 8:35:07",
   "QKEY":"Q284",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Startropics",
   "Question":"The second chapter of the game begins with you attempting to find what missing animal?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Dolphin",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Monkey",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Elephant",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Hippo",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 8:45:34",
   "QKEY":"Q285",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"Putt Putt Saves the Zoo",
   "Question":"Which animal is Zanzibar?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Hippo",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Lion",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Snake",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Giraffe",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 15:19:46",
   "QKEY":"Q286",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"FinalGamer",
   "GameTitle":"Unravel",
   "Question":"What shape is the red yarn badge that you recover at the end of \"How Much Is Enough\"?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A Spider",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A Radiation Symbol",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Human Hand",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A Heart Shape",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 15:44:17",
   "QKEY":"Q287",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"FinalGamer",
   "GameTitle":"Broken Sword: Shadow of the Templars",
   "Question":"How do you escape from the assassin Khan in Syria?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Shock him with a hand buzzer",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Blind him with a spray can",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Offer him some traditional Syrian food",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Jam a matchstick into his gun",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 21:13:08",
   "QKEY":"Q288",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"ProtoIV",
   "GameTitle":"Shin Nekketsu Kouha: Kunio-tachi No Banka",
   "Question":"How are Misako and Kyouko removed from gameplay near the end of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"They get shot by the final boss",
   "FakeAnswer1":"They betray you",
   "FakeAnswer2":"They have to go back to class",
   "FakeAnswer3":"They get caught in a trap",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 21:54:36",
   "QKEY":"Q289",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Summoboomo",
   "GameTitle":"Sweet Fuse: At Your Side",
   "Question":"Which Japanese game developer is featured briefly in this dating sim?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Keiji Inafune",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hideki Kamiya",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Hideo Kojima",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Shinji Mikami",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/3/2016 22:08:59",
   "QKEY":"Q290",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Arthur",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby series",
   "Question":"Which of these games features Dedede's Castle from the anime?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Kirby's Squeak Squad",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Kirby Super Star Ultra",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Kirby Triple Deluxe",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Kirby's Air Ride",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/4/2016 2:03:06",
   "QKEY":"Q291",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Xenosage",
   "GameTitle":"Monster Hunter 4 U",
   "Question":"Which varient/subspecies is not fought in a G Rank deciphered scroll quest?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Oroshi Kirin",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Shah Dalamadur",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Raging Brachydios",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Rusted Kushala Daora",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/4/2016 3:27:00",
   "QKEY":"Q292",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MetaMarx",
   "GameTitle":"Metal Gear Solid (series)",
   "Question":"Each game has a scene where the player must rapidly press a button to stay alive. Which is the only game to not have this?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Metal Gear Solid 5",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Metal Gear Solid 4",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Metal Gear Solid",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Metal Gear Solid: Peace Walker",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/4/2016 17:39:40",
   "QKEY":"Q293",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Little Inferno",
   "Question":"What do the four items you burn together end the game (Broken Magnet, Jar of Fireflies, Toy Exterminator, Fashionable Sunglasses) have in common, aside from the fact that you mailed them to your neighbour Sugar Plumps over the course of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"They all change the appearance of the fireplace when burned",
   "FakeAnswer1":"They can all be seen somewhere in the game's UI",
   "FakeAnswer2":"They're all mentioned by other characters, in letters",
   "FakeAnswer3":"They can't be burned by themselves",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 0:31:41",
   "QKEY":"Q294",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Smilefires",
   "GameTitle":"Pokemon Red/Blue",
   "Question":"What was the only way to get Pinsir in Pokemon Red?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"You couldn't - it was a Blue exclusive",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Catch in the Safari Zone",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Prize at the Game Corner",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Trade with an NPC",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 8:07:49",
   "QKEY":"Q295",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"UZworm",
   "GameTitle":"NBA 2k16",
   "Question":"What is your character's default nickname in the MyCareer mode?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Freq",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Jumpman",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Baller",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Crash",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 14:44:32",
   "QKEY":"Q296",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Dark Souls 3",
   "Question":"How do you obtain the White Sign Soapstone?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The Firelink Shrinemaiden sells one for 500 souls",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Firelink Firekeeper gives one to you when talked to",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Greirat of the Undead Settlement sells one for 500 souls",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Trade a Homeward Bone with Picklepum the Crow",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 21:03:53",
   "QKEY":"Q297",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"TheBaconDrinker",
   "GameTitle":"Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon",
   "Question":"Which weapon is required to defeat Gharnef in Chapter 23?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Starlight",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Falchion",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Hauteclere",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Wo Dao",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 21:41:08",
   "QKEY":"Q298",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mitcheddar93",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby's Return to Dreamland",
   "Question":"Of the new abilities that appeared in Return to Dreamland, which one actually debuted in the anime first?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Water",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Whip",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Leaf",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Spear",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 21:53:26",
   "QKEY":"Q299",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"TobiasHawk",
   "GameTitle":"Ratchet & Clank: Into The Nexus",
   "Question":"What is the song that plays while firing the RYNO VII",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Night on Bald Mountain",
   "FakeAnswer1":"1812 Overture",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ave Maria",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Rhapsody in Blue",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 21:56:32",
   "QKEY":"Q300",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Kyon2570",
   "GameTitle":"Donkey Kong 64",
   "Question":"What color bananas does Chunky Kong have to collect?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Green",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Blue",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Red",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Yellow",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 22:09:29",
   "QKEY":"Q301",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Mitcheddar93",
   "GameTitle":"Super Smash Bros. Melee",
   "Question":"Which mode must you complete with every character in order to unlock Mr. Game & Watch?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Target Test",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Home-Run Contest ",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Event Match",
   "FakeAnswer3":"All-Star Mode",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 22:20:29",
   "QKEY":"Q302",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Michael4thewin",
   "GameTitle":"Bioshock Infinite",
   "Question":"What is the nickname given to Booker DeWitt throughout the game.  ",
   "CorrectAnswer":"The False Shepard ",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The False Lamb ",
   "FakeAnswer2":"The Vox Populi",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Lost One",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 22:26:56",
   "QKEY":"Q303",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Whatthefnu",
   "GameTitle":"Mother 3",
   "Question":"Which of these enemies can be encountered more than once?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Nuclear Reactor Robot",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mystery Metal Monkey",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Top Dogfish",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Soot Dumpling",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 22:49:12",
   "QKEY":"Q304",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Michael4thewin",
   "GameTitle":"Grand Theft Auto IV",
   "Question":"In the main game of GTA IV, what is the name of Niko's cousin?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Roman ",
   "FakeAnswer1":"He doesn't have one",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Dimitri ",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Vlad",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/5/2016 23:11:29",
   "QKEY":"Q305",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Need For Speed Most Wanted",
   "Question":"What is Baron's real name?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Karl Smit",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wes Allen",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ronald McCrea",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Eugene James",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/6/2016 0:02:41",
   "QKEY":"Q306",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Fallout 4",
   "Question":"Which of the following companions is not a Synth?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Piper",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Deacon",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Paladin Danse",
   "FakeAnswer3":"X6-88",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/6/2016 0:17:35",
   "QKEY":"Q307",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Overwatch",
   "Question":"What map does Symmetra say would be a good place for a Vishkar Development?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Dorado",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Route 66",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ilios",
   "FakeAnswer3":"King's Row",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/6/2016 12:27:47",
   "QKEY":"Q308",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"SumThymeLater",
   "GameTitle":"Super Shrek Party",
   "Question":"Which character is in this game.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Fairy Godmother",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Monsieur Hood",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Fiona",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Thelonious",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/7/2016 1:33:14",
   "QKEY":"Q309",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Strider Returns",
   "Question":"Which of the following bosses does not reappear in The Master's Prison Ship",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Giant Bee",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Solo",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Grandmaster Meio",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Cyber T-REX",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/7/2016 6:04:07",
   "QKEY":"Q310",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"TackyRackyor0dd1",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby: Squeak Squad",
   "Question":"Which of these Copy Abilities is not featured in any other Kirby game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Ghost",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Magic",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Cupid",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Throw",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/7/2016 6:15:19",
   "QKEY":"Q311",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Scott Pilgrim Vs. The World: The Game",
   "Question":"Which NYC-based rock band provided the music for this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Anamanaguchi",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The Minibosses",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Freezepop",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Advantage",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/7/2016 6:21:31",
   "QKEY":"Q312",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Anamanaguchi presents: CAPSULE SILENCE XXIV",
   "Question":"What is the name of the robot who helps you navigate the Developer Sandbox and plays the tapes you find?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"F.R.U.G. UNIT",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Frug MK XXIV",
   "FakeAnswer2":"arys frug",
   "FakeAnswer3":"mr frug the friendly robot",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/7/2016 14:09:36",
   "QKEY":"Q313",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Mortal Kombat",
   "Question":"What is the only port of the game where Goro is playable?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Gameboy",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Sega CD",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Amiga",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Super Nintendo",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/8/2016 0:04:34",
   "QKEY":"Q314",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"King Green",
   "GameTitle":"Tony Hawk's Underground 2",
   "Question":"Which of these was not a playable character?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Spider-Man",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Big Foot",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Benjamin Franklin",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Shrek",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/9/2016 18:30:45",
   "QKEY":"Q315",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Extreme0",
   "GameTitle":"LISA: The Painful RPG",
   "Question":"At the start of the game, what is Brad Armstrong's default starting armor.",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Itchy Poncho",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Leather Poncho",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Damp Poncho",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Trash Bag Poncho",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 2:29:18",
   "QKEY":"Q316",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"TobiasHawk",
   "GameTitle":"Tony Hawk's Pro Skater (series)",
   "Question":"Who is NOT a playable guest character in any of the games?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Solid Snake",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Doomguy",
   "FakeAnswer2":"King Graham",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Shrek",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 20:10:07",
   "QKEY":"Q317",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"ProtoIV",
   "GameTitle":"GOD HAND",
   "Question":"Which of these is not a line from the end credits song",
   "CorrectAnswer":"God Stomp your face into oblivion",
   "FakeAnswer1":"If it's too much I grovel at your feet",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Lost a limb in a fight",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Who's next, don't be a fool",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 20:21:18",
   "QKEY":"Q318",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"D_W",
   "GameTitle":"Orcs Must Die! 2",
   "Question":"What does the passive ability of the Jar of Ghosts trinkets do?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Causes Fear on enemies that hit the player",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Creates ghostly orbs that automatically attack the nearby enemies",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Creates an aura of fear around the player",
   "FakeAnswer3":"It doesn't have a passive.",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 20:27:01",
   "QKEY":"Q319",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Magnetic North",
   "GameTitle":"Hearthstone: Heroes of Warcraft",
   "Question":"Which of the following classes has no collectable weapon cards?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Druid",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Warrior",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Shaman",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Paladin",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 20:36:03",
   "QKEY":"Q320",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"jlpbradley",
   "GameTitle":"Okami",
   "Question":"What mythical item is used to shrink Amaterasu in Sei-an City?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Lucky Mallet",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Satomi Power Orbs",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Magic Mirror",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Fox Rods",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 20:49:23",
   "QKEY":"Q321",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"LucyRomana",
   "GameTitle":"Batman: Arkham Origins",
   "Question":"What type of grenades does Batman acquire during the main game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Glue",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Ice",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Clay",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Electric",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 21:10:58",
   "QKEY":"Q322",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"FinalGamer",
   "GameTitle":"Sanitarium",
   "Question":"In \"the Innocent Abandoned\", what's the secret behind the children's Hide-and-Seek champion who has never lost a single game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"She's dead and buried in her grave",
   "FakeAnswer1":"She's not a human, she's a bird",
   "FakeAnswer2":"She's actually a statue",
   "FakeAnswer3":"She's an unborn twin in one of the children",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 21:33:41",
   "QKEY":"Q323",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Koobes",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy V",
   "Question":"Which animal is not summoned by the Ranger's !Animals ability",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bear",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Squirrel",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Unicorn",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Falcon",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 21:40:19",
   "QKEY":"Q324",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"sprankton",
   "GameTitle":"Nethack",
   "Question":"What happens if you fly or levitate over a sink?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"You crash to the ground.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A geyser of water hits you.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Nothing",
   "FakeAnswer3":".You drop one of your rings down the drain.",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/10/2016 22:00:27",
   "QKEY":"Q325",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Zero Escape: 9 Persons 9 Hours 9 Doors",
   "Question":"Where does your character get trapped as part of the puzzle behind door #4?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"A freezer",
   "FakeAnswer1":"A bathroom",
   "FakeAnswer2":"A Closet",
   "FakeAnswer3":"A Jail Cell",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 0:05:27",
   "QKEY":"Q326",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Turok: Dinosaur Hunter",
   "Question":"The Longhunter is the first enemy you encounter to wield, and drop upon defeat, what weapon?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Pulse Rifle",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Grenade Launcher",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Minigun",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Auto-Shotgun",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 3:16:10",
   "QKEY":"Q327",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Dustminion",
   "GameTitle":"Mega Man 8",
   "Question":"Which pair of NES-era robot masters appeared as bosses in the Saturn version only?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Cut Man and Wood Man",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Elec Man and Quick Man",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Metal Man and Snake Man",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Guts Man and Napalm Man",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 4:54:19",
   "QKEY":"Q328",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MetaMarx",
   "GameTitle":"Kirby: Planet Robobot",
   "Question":"The Robobot Armor can use all of the following abilities EXCEPT...",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Hammer",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wheel",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Parasol",
   "FakeAnswer3":"ESP",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 11:00:06",
   "QKEY":"Q329",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Fallout New Vegas",
   "Question":"What happens in the year 2910?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Blind Diode Jefferson saves Big MT from the Sonic Invasion.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"The NCR bans the use of all other Acronyms.",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Brotherhood and Enclave sign a peace treaty, and they both trick the other and wipe themselves out.",
   "FakeAnswer3":"The Courier's distant son builds a magic ice cream truck and flies around the universe, spreading joy to children everywhere.",
   "Difficulty":4
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 14:46:08",
   "QKEY":"Q330",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"inthesto",
   "GameTitle":"Street Fighter 3: Third Strike",
   "Question":"Kara-throws are a glitch commonly used in competitive play. Why is it generally used?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"To extend the range of a throw",
   "FakeAnswer1":"To increase the damage of a throw",
   "FakeAnswer2":"To give a throw invincibility from strike",
   "FakeAnswer3":"To make throws build up extra super meter",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 19:32:45",
   "QKEY":"Q331",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Xenosage",
   "GameTitle":"Tales of Vesperia",
   "Question":"Which mysic arte was not usable in the Xbox 360 version?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Indignation",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Savage Wolf Fury",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Ancient Catastrophe",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Overlord Reign Impact",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/11/2016 21:33:46",
   "QKEY":"Q332",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Dark Cloud",
   "Question":"Which dungeon has a glitched back floor key that never spawns?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Gallery of Time",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Wise Owl Forest",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Sun And Moon Temple",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Divine Beast Cave",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 3:31:10",
   "QKEY":"Q333",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MetaMarx",
   "GameTitle":"Monster Hunter 3 Ultimate",
   "Question":"How does Brachydios re-apply slime to its fists?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"It licks its fists",
   "FakeAnswer1":"It buries its fists into the ground",
   "FakeAnswer2":"It dips its fists in lava",
   "FakeAnswer3":"It dips its fists in water",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 3:48:44",
   "QKEY":"Q334",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MetaMarx",
   "GameTitle":"Monster Hunter Freedom Unite",
   "Question":"Which of the following monsters made their debut in this game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Queen Vespoid",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Yama Tsukami",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Rathalos",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Diablos",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 4:26:48",
   "QKEY":"Q335",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"MetaMarx",
   "GameTitle":"Monster Hunter 4 Ultimate",
   "Question":"What special property do Seregios weapons have?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"They sharpen after a certain amount of dodge rolls",
   "FakeAnswer1":"They apply bleed",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Every attack you successfully dodge raises the weapon's affinity by 2%",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Successfully landing an attack will raise your attack stat until you are hit",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 10:10:23",
   "QKEY":"Q336",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Fire Emblem: Fates",
   "Question":"Which of these characters is recruitable in both the Conquest and Birthright versions of the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Kaze",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Hinata",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Arthur",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Saizo",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 11:58:22",
   "QKEY":"Q337",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Turok 2: Seeds Of Evil",
   "Question":"What level does not have an energy totem to defend?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Primagen's Lightship",
   "FakeAnswer1":"River Of Souls",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Hive of the Mantids",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Death Marshes",
   "Difficulty":2
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 14:42:05",
   "QKEY":"Q338",
   "HasSeen":true,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Megaman X (Series)",
   "Question":"What is the only game to not have unique stage select music for when the fortress stages are open?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Megaman X6",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Megaman X4",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Megaman X2",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Megaman X8",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 15:41:32",
   "QKEY":"Q339",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"g0m",
   "GameTitle":"Warioware: D.I.Y",
   "Question":"Which recurring Warioware character teaches the player the basics of creating their own microgames?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Penny Crygor",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Mike",
   "FakeAnswer2":"9-Volt",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Mona",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 16:04:37",
   "QKEY":"Q340",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Thevideogameraptorboggle",
   "GameTitle":"Borderlands",
   "Question":"Where do you find the only Vladof produced Shotgun in the game?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"It is Brick's Starting weapon.",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Obtained through a glitch",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Completing a side quest",
   "FakeAnswer3":"In The Secret Armory of General Knoxx DLC",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 16:16:49",
   "QKEY":"Q341",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"ZincAlloy",
   "GameTitle":"Bubble Bobble",
   "Question":"In the Japanese version of the game, the final boss was named \"Super Drunk\". What was his localized name in English Arcade versions?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Grumple Grommit",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Willy Whistle",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bubble Buster",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Baron von Blubba",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 16:46:56",
   "QKEY":"Q342",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Smite",
   "GameTitle":"Chrono Trigger",
   "Question":"You can steal this pointless weapon from the Nu in the prehistoric hunting grounds! What is it?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Mop",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Stone Arm",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Plunger",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Egg Cannon",
   "Difficulty":3
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 16:50:17",
   "QKEY":"Q343",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"???",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy III",
   "Question":"Which job can throw weapons at enemies?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Ninja",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Samurai",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Monk",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Chuckster",
   "Difficulty":1
 },
 {
   "Timestamp":"6/12/2016 16:53:40",
   "QKEY":"Q344",
   "HasSeen":false,
   "Submitter":"Trivial Man",
   "GameTitle":"Final Fantasy V",
   "Question":"What is the canonical English name of the main male protagonist?",
   "CorrectAnswer":"Bartz",
   "FakeAnswer1":"Butz",
   "FakeAnswer2":"Bust",
   "FakeAnswer3":"Bort",
   "Difficulty":1
 }
]